https://www.haleproducts.com/customer-support-privacy/

Cookie Policy
This site uses and sets "cookies" on your computer to help make this website better.
We use cookies to remember log-in details and provide secure log-in, collect statistics to optimize site functionality, and deliver content tailored to your interests. Click accept to give your consent to accept cookies and go directly to the site or click on more information to see detailed descriptions of the types of cookies we store.
Click here to learn about cookie settings.
Accept
Decline
Service Partner Locator
Customer Support
Contact Customer Support
Find Product Expert
Find Service Partner (FAST)
Product Returns
Warranty
Certifications
Tech Resource Center
Hale Training Academy
My Account Log In
About Us
Press Room
Trade Shows & Events
Careers
Your Language:
Hale Products
Hale Products Chinese
Need Assistance?
+1 (800) 533-3569
My Product Request -
Items
0
(0)
You have no selected items.
All
All
SAM
Fire Pumps
Vehicle Electronics
Engine Driven Units
Foam & CAFs
Pump Flow Solutions
Engine Driven UnitsPortable Pumps
Floats & Packs (Special Purpose)
High Pressure / Low Volume (Wild Land)
Medium Pressure / Medium Volume Attack
Low Pressure / High Volume (High Flow)
Skids & Trailers
Skids & Trailers
Foam & CAFsFoam
SmartFoam
CAFs
SmartCAFS
Accessories
EZ-Fill
We Are Committed to Your Right to Privacy
Hale Products Company (“Hale Products”)  respects your right to privacy. We developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about our practices. Questions regarding this Privacy Statement should be directed to auber@idexcorp.com.Privacy is a concern to most Internet users. Hale Products is acutely aware of, and sensitive to, the privacy concerns of our customers. We assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. If you are registering to use the site you will be asked to provide certain information. We are asking for this information solely for the purpose of providing the services offered and authenticating your identity when you login.Privacy Policy EnforcementIf you feel that Hale Products is violating this Privacy Statement, please contact us at auber@idexcorp.com.Use of Postal & Email AddressesWe occasionally make the names, postal addresses, and email addresses of our customers available to highly screened companies that offer products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these third-party offers, please let us know by contacting Hale Products at 1.800.533.3569.Traffic DataWe collect click-stream data such as referring URL, browser and platform, time of visit, pages visited and searches performed. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our website and better serve our customers. We analyze this data to establish trends and help us improve your online experience. Aggregated traffic data may be shared with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners for demographic purposes. When used in this aggregated form no one will be able to identify or contact you.Use of E-mail AddressesWhen you register on haleproducts.com, you may receive email promotions from time to time. To unsubscribe from these emails, follow the unsubscribe directions contained in the email so that you may opt-out of future e-mails. E-mails that confirm business transactions will always be sent to you.Use of CookiesA "cookie" is a text file that our website sends to your browser to store your preferences. Cookies allow our website to "remember" information about your preferences either until you exit your current browser window (if the cookie is temporary) or until you disable or delete the cookie. Many users prefer to use cookies to help them navigate a website as seamlessly as possible. We use "cookies" to enhance your experience on our site. You should be aware that cookies contain no more information than you volunteer, and they are not able to "invade" your hard drive and return to the sender with personal or other information from your computer. If you choose not to accept a cookie, you are still welcome at our website; however we will not be able to accept online orders.Sending You Responses and UpdatesWe generally respond to any e-mail questions, requests for service or information, and other inquiries we receive. We may also retain this correspondence to improve our products, services and website. Frequently we retain contact information so that we can send individuals updates or other important information about our services and products.SurveysFrom time-to-time we may request information via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you always have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve this website, and to improve our customer service and product offerings.Terms of UseThe Hale Products website may contain links to third-party sites. The linked sites are not under the control of Hale Products, and Hale Products is not responsible for the contents of any linked site, any link contained in a linked site, any changes or updates to such linked sites, or any transmission from any linked site. Hale Products is providing these links to third-party sites only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Hale Products of the site.License and Site AccessHale Products grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of Hale Products. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of this site or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of Hale Products. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of akronbrass.com so long as the link does not portray Hale Products, its parent company, or their products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use any Hale Products logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission.CopyrightThe site and the content within the site are the property of Hale Products or its affiliates and are protected by United States copyright laws and international treaty provisions. The compilation, organization and display of the content as well as all software and inventions used on and in connection with this Site are the exclusive property of Hale Products. These materials may not be copied or redistributed for any for any purposes without prior written permission from Hale Products.Trademark Information
1TOUCH, AnodePro, CLASS 1, ES-KEY, EZFILL, FOAMLOGIX, FYR FLOTE, FYR PAK, GODIVA, Godiva Smartfoam, HALE, QMAX, SIDE KICK,SMARTCAFS, SmartFOAM, SWIFT HANDLE, TORRENT, TWISTER and ULTRAVIEW are registered trademarks of Hale Products. All other registered and/or unregistered trademarks displayed on this site constitute the intellectual property of their respective holders.
x
Add to Cart
Price:
Actual Price:
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price."
As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
You have no obligation to purchase the product once you know the price. You can simply remove the item from your cart.
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price."
As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
You have no obligation to purchase the product once you know the price. You can simply remove the item from your cart.
Customer Support
Find a Product Expert
Service Partner Locator (FAST)
Returns (RMA)
Warranty
Hale Training Academy
Class Registration
Resource Center
Products
Pumps
Vehicle Electronics
Engine Driven Units
Foam & CAFS
Pump Kit Modules
Parts & Accessories
Customer Support
Contact Us
Find Product Expert
Find Service Partner (FAST)
Product Returns
Warranty
Tech Resource Center
About Us
Company Information
Press Room
Trade Shows & Events
Careers
Need Assistance
Need Assistance?
+1 (800) 533-3569
Find Us Online
IDEX | Akron Brass | AWG | Hale | Godiva | Weldon
Hale Products Inc.
Hale Products is committed to offering the highest level of service and performance for rescue personnel and fire truck manufacturers. Consisting of three brands - Hale, Class 1 and Godiva, Hale Products is a leader in fire suppression pumps, plumbing, valves, foam, CAFS, electronic, gauges and
ES-key multiplexing systems.
Select Store:
© 2017 Hale. All rights reserved.
Forgot?
Login
Close Window
Continue shopping
Back to top
